♪ ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT HISTORY ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH BIOLOGY ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT A SCIENCE BOOK ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT
THE FRENCH I TOOK ♪
♪ BUT I DO KNOW
THAT I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ AND I KNOW THAT
IF YOU LOVE ME TOO ♪
♪ WHAT A WONDERFUL
WORLD THIS WOULD BE ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT
GEOGRAPHY ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH TRIGONOMETRY ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT ALGEBRA ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW WHAT A
SLIDE RULE IS FOR ♪
♪ BUT I DO KNOW ONE
AND ONE IS TWO ♪
♪ AND IF THIS ONE
COULD BE WITH YOU ♪
♪ WHAT A WONDERFUL
WORLD THIS WOULD BE ♪
♪ NOW I DON'T CLAIM
TO BE AN 'A' STUDENT ♪
♪ BUT I'M TRYING TO BE ♪
♪ FOR MAYBE BY BEING
AN 'A' STUDENT, BABY ♪
♪ I CAN WIN YOUR LOVE FOR ME ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT HISTORY ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH BIOLOGY ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT A SCIENCE BOOK ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT
THE FRENCH I TOOK ♪
♪ BUT I DO KNOW THAT
I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ AND I KNOW THAT
IF YOU LOVE ME TOO ♪
♪ WHAT A WONDERFUL
WORLD THIS WOULD BE ♪
♪ AH - TA TA TA ♪
♪ HISTORY ♪
♪ BIOLOGY ♪
♪ AH - TA TA TA ♪
♪ SCIENCE BOOK ♪
♪ FRENCH I TOOK, YEAH ♪
♪ BUT I DO KNOW THAT
I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ AND I KNOW THAT
IF YOU LOVE ME TOO ♪
♪ WHAT A WONDERFUL
WORLD THIS WOULD BE ♪
♪ ♪